Multi-lang Readme cuz i was bored

== AI_EN ==

Descriptions:
This is for work & storage of SQLs untested, or not yet verified, or checked by DBT
its is for anything AI meaning EAI/SAI/or random trash handling thats done by other means 
needed to get things working and inplace
General Dirs include:
* Dungeons 
-(not raid) (Reg,Hero)

* Raids    
- (not dungeons) (10/25)

* Questing 
- (daily/weekly/holiday/instanced-world) 

* Texts    
- (Script_text/ceature_text/npc_text/Page_texts/Gossips)

* Mobs     
- (Trash/formations/Scripts/Loot)(non-Boss npcs, or vendor/trainer/gaurds)

* WayPoints  
- (this is all wp's (wpdata/wp_script/generally any thing that has anything to do with movement)

Keep inmind this is open to public and who ever has something to offer.
so keep the directories plain and simple and easy to browse, 
or the will be subject to deletion.

and as stated in previous readme, everything here-in is NOT approved yet for 
public use it is developmental sql area, so there is NO SUPPORT,
if you use any of these the issues that can be caused is yours alone.

---------------------------------------------------------------------

== AI_ES ==

Descripciones:
Esto es para trabajo & almacenamiento de SQLs untested, aún no se ha verificado o comprobados por TDC
su es para nada AI significa basura aleatoria EAI/SAI/o manipulación thats hechos por otros medios 
necesarios para conseguir cosas trabajando y in-situ
general Dirs incluyen:
* Mazmorras
- (no raid) (Reg, héroe)

* Incursiones
- (no mazmorras) (10/25)

* Questing
- (diario y semanal y vacaciones instanciado-Mundial) 

* textos
- (Script_text/ceature_text/npc_text/Page_texts/cotilleos)

* Turbas
- (Trash/formaciones/Scripts/botín) (PNJ no Boss o proveedor, formador/gaurds)

* WayPoints
- (esto es del todo wp (wpdata/wp_script/generalmente cualquier cosa que tenga algo que ver con el movimiento)

Mantener inmind está abierto al público y que nunca tiene algo que ofrecer.
así que los directorios llano y simple y fácil para examinar o la voluntad de ser objeto de eliminación.

y como se indica en el archivo Léame anterior, todo aquí en no está aprobada para uso 
público es área de desarrollo de sql, por lo que hay sin soporte,
Si utiliza alguno de estos los temas que pueden ser causados es tuyo solo.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

== AI_RU ==

Описания:
Это для работы & хранения SQLs неопробованные, еще не проверены или проверены ПБУ
его для что-нибыдь AI смысл EAI/SAI/или случайный мусор, обработка thats сделано при помощи других средств, 
необходимых для получения вещи работать и inplace
Генеральный Dirs включают в себя:
* Подземелья
- (не raid) (Reg, герой)

* Рейды
- (не подземелья) (10/25)

* Новаторский
- (ежедневно/еженедельно/праздник/экземплярами мир) 

* тексты
- (Script_text/ceature_text/npc_text/Page_texts/слухи)

* Толпой
- (мусор/образований/скрипты/грабить) (РНУ босс, или поставщик/преподаватель/gaurds)

* GameObjects
- (объекты, пропавших из мира/экземплярами/Квест/вызвал/doodads/постепенно/тайм)

* WayPoints
- (это все wp (wpdata/wp_script/вообще любую вещь которая имеет ничего общего с движением)

Держите inmind это открыто для общественности и кто всегда есть что предложить.
так держать каталоги равнины и простой и легкой для просмотра, или будет подвергаться удаления.

как указано в предыдущих readme, все здесь не утверждает для публичного использования это области развития sql, 
так что без поддержки, и
Если вы используете любой из этих вопросов, которые могут быть вызваны твое одиночку.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

== AI_FR ==

Description :
C'est pour le travail & stockage de SQLs non testés, non encore vérifiées ou vérifié par DBT
sa est pour quoi que ce soit AI signifie EAI/SAI/ou trash aléatoire c'est fait par d'autres moyens 
nécessaires pour obtenir ce travail et inplace de manutention
Général Dirs comprennent :
* Donjons
- (non raid) (Reg, Hero)

* Raids
- (pas de donjons) (10/25)

* Quêtes
- (quotidien/hebdomadaire/vacances/instancié-monde) 

* textes 
- (Script_text/ceature_text/npc_text/Page_texts/potins)

* Les foules
- (Trash/formations/Scripts/butin) (non-Boss NPC ou vendeur/formateur/gaurds)

* GameObjects
- (objets absent du monde/instancié/quête/convoqué/bidules/progressive/chronométrée)

* Points de cheminement
- (il s'agit de tous les wp (wpdata/wp_script/généralement quelque chose qui a rien à voir avec le mouvement)

Gardez nous c'est ouvert au public et qui a quelque chose à offrir.
donc garder les répertoires ordinaire et simple et facile à parcourir, 
ou la volonté faire l'objet d'une suppression.

et comme indiqué dans le readme précédente, tout en l'espèce n'est pas approuvé encore pour le public, 
c'est zone de développement sql, donc il n'y a aucun soutien,
Si vous utilisez une de ces questions qui peuvent être causées est vôtre seul.

///End